A Finding Aid to the Jamison Thomas Gallery Records, 1940-2000, bulk 1980-1995, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artists' Files, 1940-1996; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 14 Linear feet Boxes 14-28
  - Grenon, Gregory, 1988-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - Grenon, Gregory-Historical File, 1987-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Grenon, Gregory-Photos, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Grgich, Anne, 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
  - Grgich, Anne-Slides, 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 9-11)
  - Halley, Peter-Slides, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Hammer, Gary, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Harris, Alfred, 1986-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 14-16)
  - Hart, Claudia, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Henry, Patricia, 1983-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Herdlein, Robert, 1989-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 19-22)
  - Herdlein, Robert-Photographs, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 23-24)
  - Herdlein, Robert-Photographs, 1990-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Hutchison, Heather, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Illsley, Bryan, 1989-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
  - Illsley, Bryan-Photos, 1986-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Illsley, Bryan-Slides, 1981-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Jacobson, Bill, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Kadar, Kevin, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Kerns, Maude, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Kerns, Maude-Slides, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Kershnik, Brian, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Kettlewell, George, 1981-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Kline, Steve, 1989-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Krug, Margaret, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Kruger, Barbara, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Larson, Steve, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Lasker, Johnathan, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Lauman, Chris, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Laurnen, Chris, 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Lawrence, Jim, 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Lockhart, Lisa, 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Le Witt, Sol, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Loose Materials, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Macdonald, Marjorie, 1983-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 24-25)
  - Mangold, Robert-Slides, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Mapplethorpe, Robert, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Mason, Alden, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Mason, Alden, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - May, Dan, 1980-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 2-7)
  - Mayer, Jerry, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Mayer, Maurice, 1990-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 9-10)
  - Mentor, Will, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Black and White Negatives, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Monza, Louis, 1940-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 13-16)
  - Monza, Louis-Slides, 1949-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 17-18)
  - Moore, Tom, 1982-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Mossaed, Mahwash, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Motherell, Robert, 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Mozenter, Cynthia, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Nakada, Thomas, 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 23-24)
  - Nakada, Thomas-Photos, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Nakada, Thomas-Slides, 1990-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 2-4)
  - Nathan, Charles, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Nicholas, Dave, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Norby, Deb, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Orr, Georgiana, 1980-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 8-11)
  - Overbay, Paula, 1981-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 12-13)
  - Overbay, Paula-Photos, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Paquette, Virginia, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Perussi, Anton, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Peterson, Stan, 1982-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 17-20)
  - Phillips, Curtis, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Photo Album, Unidentified Artwork, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 22-24)
  - Pitt, Susan-Slides, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Podemski, Esther, 1990-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
  - Raymond, Raymond, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Reinsch, Walter, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
  - Rust, David, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Rust, David-Slides, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Ryman, Robert, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Seijas, Jaff, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Serl, Jon, 1981-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 11-20)
  - Serl, Jon-Files, 1947-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Serl, Jon-Lindy Allison (Art Sales), 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Serl, Jon-Most Important Articles, 1981-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Serl, Jon-Payments to Artists, 1987-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 24-25)
  - Serl, Jon-Photographs, Medium, circa 1980s-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Serl, Jon-Photographs and Negatives, circa 1980s-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Serl, Jon-Photos, Small, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Serl, Jon-Will and Estate, 1985-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Seubert, Susan, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Seubert, Susan-Photos, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Southern Folk Pottery-Various Artists Slides, 1989-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 6-7)
  - Stotik, Eric, 1985-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 8-13)
  - Stotik, Eric-Photos, 1987-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Sveitch, Vinson, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 15-16)
  - Thomas, James David, 1989-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 17-18)
  - Thomas, James David-Photos, 1986-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Tracy, Jay, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Tracy, Jay-Photos, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Tracy, Jay-Slides, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Truong, Tan, 1983-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Unfiled Snapshots and Negatives, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Valdivieso, Yvonne, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Van Sant, Gus, 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
  - Van Sant, Gus-Photos, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Van Sant, Gus-Slides, 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Vidor, Molly, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Vidor, Molly-Photos, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Vidor, Molly-Slides, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Wagner, D.R., 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 10-11)
  - Wague, Diakite Baba-Photographs, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Warren, Wally, 1985-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 13-15)
  - Watts, Todd-Slide, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Wendel, Peter, 1985-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Wesselmann, Tom, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - William Jamison Memorial, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Wimmer, Ted, 1979-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 20-24)
  - Wimmer, Ted-Inventory, 1986-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 25-26)
  - Winer, Ed, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Yoder, Henry B., 1984-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Yoder, Robert, 1989-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Yoder, Robert-Slides, 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Zimmerman, Philip, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 4-5)